Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
In this lesson, we will practice English
في هذا الدرس، سنمارس اللغة الإنجليزية
for the gas station,
لمحطة الوقود،
how to ask for fuel
كيف تطلب الوقود
how to buy something from the shop
كيفية شراء شيء من المتجر
how to ask for directions politely.
كيف تطلب الاتجاهات بأدب.
Have you ever visited a gas station abroad
هل سبق لك أن زرت محطة وقود في الخارج
and felt nervous about speaking English, or
وشعرت بالتوتر عند التحدث بالإنجليزية، أو
didn't understand what the staff was saying?
لم تفهم ما يقوله الموظفون؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
With this video, you will feel more confident
مع هذا الفيديو، ستشعر بثقة أكبر
and prepared.
ومستعدا.
Let me tell you a short, simple story.
دعوني أخبركم قصة قصيرة وبسيطة.
It's about the time I stopped at a gas station
كان الوقت تقريبا عندما توقفت عند محطة وقود
while driving in another country.
أثناء القيادة في بلد آخر.